Lesson 15.
Nicole practices her election speech.
Nicole is running for student body president.
She must give a speech next week.
She discusses this speech with her mother.
What's up, Nicole?
I pulled an all-nighter working on my election speech.
No wonder you look like a basket case.
Did you finish your speech?
Yes.
At 6 a.m.
That must be a load off your mind.
It's not.
I've got to give the speech tomorrow in front of 1,500 people.
I'm a nervous wreck.
Just remember the old rule of thumb.
Imagine your audience naked.
That's gross.
Why would I want to do that?
According to conventional wisdom, it'll make you less nervous.
Only practice will do the trick.
Okay, let's hear the speech.
Good afternoon, everyone.
There are four candidates running for president.
You think you have several choices.
In reality, you have just one choice.
Me?
You can't say that.
You'll turn off your audience immediately.
It sounds like I have a big head.
I'll say.